One of my bad habits is saying “busy” when people ask me how I’m doing.
我的坏习惯之一，就是别人问我过得怎么样时，我会回答“忙”。
Sometimes it’s because I actually am busy, but other times it’s because that’s what I think I’m supposed to say.
有时是因为我确实很忙，但另一些时候，是因为我觉得自己就应该这么说。
That’s what important people say.
大人物就是这么说的。
That’s what people who get promoted say.
得到晋升的人就是这么说的。
But working long hours doesn’t drive better results.
但长时间工作并不能带来更好的成果。
Never taking a vacation won’t lead to a promotion.
从不休假并不会带来晋升。
So why are we so proud to talk about how busy we are all the time?
那么，我们为什么总是如此自豪地谈论自己有多忙呢？
In 2016, researchers from Columbia, Harvard, and Georgetown conducted a study to figure it out.
2016年，哥伦比亚大学、哈佛大学和乔治城大学的研究人员开展了一项研究，想要弄清楚这个问题。
They found busy people are perceived to be of high status, and interestingly, these status attributions are heavily influenced by our own beliefs about social mobility.
他们发现，忙碌的人被视为地位高的人；有趣的是，这种地位认定在很大程度上受我们自己对社会流动性的看法影响。
In other words, the more we believe that one has the opportunity for success based on hard work, the more we tend to think that people who skip leisure and work all the time are of higher standing.
换句话说，我们越相信一个人有机会凭借努力获得成功，就越倾向于认为那些放弃休闲、总在工作的人地位更高。
That’s why we feel like we have to appear busy, and there’s a real perception that if someone is knee-deep in meetings, emails and stress, then they’re probably a big deal.
正因如此，我们觉得自己必须显得很忙；而且人们确实有这样一种看法：如果一个人深陷于会议、邮件和压力之中，那他很可能是个大人物。
This culture of busyness is making it hard for employees to find work-life balance.
这种忙碌文化正使员工难以找到工作与生活之间的平衡。
According to a recent study, one in five highly engaged employees are at risk of burnout.
根据最近的一项研究，在高度投入工作的员工中，有五分之一面临精疲力竭的风险。
Personally, I’m going to stop saying “busy” when people ask me how I am.
就我个人而言，以后别人问我过得怎么样时，我不会再回答“忙”了。
It sounds self-righteous and sets the wrong tone.
这样说听起来自以为是，还会定下错误的基调。
Phrases like “I have limited access to email” and “I’ll respond as soon as I get back” sound like you’re being held against your will from working as opposed to making the most of your time off.
像“我收发邮件受限”“我一回来就回复”这样的说法，听起来好像有人违背你的意愿，拦着不让你工作，而不是你在充分利用休假时间。
That’s why we recently launched the Out of Office Email Generator, a free tool you can use before your next long weekend or trip.
正因如此，我们最近推出了“外出邮件自动回复生成器”，这是一款免费工具，你可以在下一个长周末或下一次出行前使用。
You can share loud and proud that you won’t be checking email until you’re back.
你可以理直气壮地告诉大家：回来之前，你都不会查看邮件。
Managers need to think twice about emailing their teams on the weekend and talking about how busy they are.
管理者需要三思：是否要在周末给团队发邮件，以及是否要谈论自己有多忙。
Leaders should take time off themselves and encourage employees to do the same.
领导者自己应该休假，并鼓励员工也这样做。